[{"answer": "The very latest, Wolf, is I'm actually standing here, John Boehner, the House Speaker's office is back there, one of his top lieutenants just came out and said there is no deal, no deal.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "What is the very latest, Dana?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "It could be if he's in the place where he can offer something.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Is that fair?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Well, Wolf, lately, in the last few hours or so, things have been very quiet here.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "What are you hearing from your sources, Dan?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Wolf, the indication we were getting was that the president -- there was a good chance the president would come out and say something tonight.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "Either way, no matter what happens, is it fair to say that we will definitely hear from the president of the United States tonight, Dan, before this midnight deadline?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Well, that's an excellent point on the last point.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "So, how is that even possible that there could be a shutdown?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "Well, this isn't anything new, Wolf.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Is the issue right now -- based on everything you know, Congresswoman -- the money, the amount of cuts that are proposed in this budget, or is it some of the social issues like funding for Planned Parenthood?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "Well, again, we don't know because the negotiations are only being handled by John Boehner, the vice president, the president and Harry Reid.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "Well, what's the sticking point right now, based on what you know?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "The speaker needs to be able to do his negotiations.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "Are you telling me that the speaker isn't consulting with key members, like you, especially given your influence among those who support the Tea Party movement?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "Well, what -- no, what I have said from the beginning is I can't vote for any deal that doesn't defund Obamacare.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Can we assume, Congresswoman, that whatever the speaker of the House, John Boehner, agrees to will be good enough for your vote?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "Of course not.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "So, you're -- are you speaking -- excuse me for interrupting -- but are you speaking, you think, for the vast majority of those Tea Party activists in the House of Representatives?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "I think people all over the country have been telling us fight, keep fighting.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "Do you agree with a lot of conservative Republicans, including Karl Rove, and Mike Huckabee, that there's got to be a deal that averts a government shutdown, otherwise this could be a political disaster for Republicans right now, just as the shutdown back in '95 turned out to be a political disaster for the Republicans then?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Well, Wolf, we'll make a decision probably sometime early this summer.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "Quick question before I let you go, are you in the Republican presidential contest?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Oh, I'm not worried at all, because, again, I think that the contest is only early on and starting.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "How worried wore you about challenging Donald Trump for the party's nomination?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "Well, we'll let you know in early June.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "How does this sound to you, Trump-Bachmann or Bachmann- Trump, how does that ticket sound to you?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "Well, I'm getting that everybody understands -- at least the leaders understand that they need to get a deal, that the American public wants a deal.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "What's the latest guidance you're getting about deal or no deal?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Well, I'm thinking it would be what I would be called a comprehensive deal that would come in more than one part.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "What's your understanding?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "LYBURN: Oh, yes.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "This continuing -- this resolution, this budget will continue to fund the health care law, is that right?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "Well, remember, Planned Parenthood is a small part of what we call Title X funding.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "What about funding for -- what about funding for Planned Parenthood?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "Well, Wolf, I've never seen anything like it.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Has it always been a sensitive issue or is this an unusually -- an unusual moment for Planned Parenthood based on your history right now?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "Well, the way I would put it is we're actually the largest family planning provider in the country.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "I -- here's what I do know: we're the largest family planning provider in the United States.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "Is Planned Parenthood -- your critics make this point and they have advertisements that make this point -- the largest abortion provider in the United States?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "And I think one thing that is really, really -- I haven't counted, you know, what services every health care provider provides in this country.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "Is it the largest abortion provider, too?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Well, I think first we should make clear that operations in Afghanistan aren't going to be affected, because they're funded by a part of the budget kind of immune to this shutdown.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "What are you hearing over there?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "It's very early days.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "In terms of morale, in terms of fighting spirit, are you getting any indication at all that this debate that's under way in Washington is impacting the ability of the U.S. military to do their jobs on the battlefield?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "That's correct.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "You don't have a whole lot of money in the bank, do you?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "Right now, I just put my husband's truck up for sale.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "How much money, if I may ask, do you have in the bank?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "Even for a week, yes, sir.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "You would be in deep trouble if that paycheck stopped even for a week?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "I'm very frightened.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "So how scared are you right now?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "My son knows a little bit about what's going on.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Have you had a chance to talk at all about this with your son?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Look, I'm disgusted with both sides.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "David, what do you think about that?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "Well, I hope that's not true.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "Do you agree, Ashwin, that from time to time, and probably right now, the fighting men and women of the United States, the U.S. military personnel are merely some sort of poker chips, if you will, being used by both political parties?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "I'm one of those people that are outraged by it.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Is that what you're hearing?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "No, I don't think there's a split.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Is this a significant split or is it overblown?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "No, that's not right at all.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "You believe, based on the experience that you as a Republican leader had in '95 during the last government shutdown -- you want a deal right now, under any circumstances, is that right?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "Well, the fact of the matter is we have a Congress -- and today I work with grassroots activists known as the Tea Party movement.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "What's a deal breaker for you?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "I don't know what the deal is, Wolf.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "Are you going to vote for this deal tonight?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "What I'm saying is I'll consider reasonable proposals.", "docId": "110408pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "Is that what you're saying, congressman?", "qSentId": 600}]